Guide to the Byron Rufus Newton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Special Files, Circa 1880s, 1887, 1891-1927; Series III; .75 linear feet (2 boxes)
  - Biographical: newspaper clippings about Byron Newton and Treasury Dept. activities
    - 1892, 1900, 1901, 1913-1916, 1918, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Expense accounts and other financial records, 1887, 1891, 1892, 1898, 1900, 1909-1912, 1913, 1916, 1918, 1927, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Memorabilia, family, 1925-1926, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Memorabilia and invitations, 1887, 1892-1893, 1895, 1898-1899, 1900, 1903, 1905, 1907, 1910-1912, 1914-1917, 1924, 1927 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings, miscellaneous, 1908, 1912, 1914, 1924, 1927, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photographs
    - of Byron R. Newton, 1914, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - of Woodrow Wilson and family, 1912, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - of William G. McAdoo, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1915, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, Circa 1880, 1898, 1908, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Printed matter
    - Miscellaneous, 1919, 1921, 1923, 1926, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - about Woodrow Wilson, 1910-1912, 1922, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Woodrow Wilson campaign material written by Byron R. Newton
    - 1912, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - 192[?], undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1912, 1913, 1916, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Oversize Material (Box 8)